go-optic.com 2008-12-17

# [Go-Optic] Store Policies & Customer Privacy

| Store Policies:  
---  
1.) Go-Optic.com (a SM of Eye Trends USA, Inc.) reserves the right to refuse service to anyone.

2.) After an order has successfully been placed with our company, cancellation of an item (or items) in your order may result in a cancellation fee, which is 10% of the cancelled items price. Shipping fee's will be excluded in this fee and cancellation of back-ordered Items will not be subject to cancellation fee's.

3.) Cancellation of lenses, lens coatings & tints (for glasses) may result in a cancellation fee of 30% on the lenses, the glasses will hold the same cancellation fee as in Section 2 (listed above). This cancellation fee will help us cover any non-recoverable expenses which have already been incurred.

4.) Customers that order prescription eyeglasses that are full rim-less (lens drilling and mounting necessary) will be responsible an additional charge of $20 for drilling & mounting. The drilling & mounting fee is sometimes included, and is displayed that it is being included, in the lens price when selecting a lens type for your full rimless glasses, however this is not always guaranteed. We will contact the customer and confirm if there is a price change of this sort, before we continue processing their order.

5.) Your credit card will not be charged any funds over your grand total order amount, unless we have received your confirmation to allow us to charge of any additional funds if necessary. Otherwise your order can be cancelled without being charged any cancellation fee.

6.) International customer orders will be responsible for all customs fee's, tax's or any other fee's associated with the delivery of their ordered merchandise.

7.) All back-ordered items will be kept on order unless the customer has requested for it to be canceled. There will be no cancellation fee's on items which are on back-order.

8.) Back-order dates are estimated and may change (sooner or later) due to the availability of the product provided by the designated manufacturer(s) and/or distributor(s).

9.) All prescription eyeglass/contact lens orders will be processed according to the information we have been provided by the patient's doctor. Go-Optic.com (a SM of Eye Trends USA, Inc.) cannot alter a patient's prescription under any circumstance.

10.) Go-Optic.com (a SM of Eye Trends USA, Inc.) and/or it's business partners reserves the right to call the eye care provider(s) referred to in the order to confirm the prescription or any other information that is necessary to process a prescription order, and we may also request a copy of your prescription for our records. 

11.) All trademarks, product names, and company names and logos appearing on this web site are the property of their respective owners. This is a private web site not endorsed or affiliated with these companies. Information provided is believed to be accurate but not guaranteed.

12.) Each shipping address update/redirection request will be an additional fee, which is the customers responsibility, of $10 which helps cover the FedEx rate expense for this type of request.

13.) Due to certain frame styles and/or prescriptions, Custom lenses can require additional expenses due to the additional materials or labor used to fill custom lens requests. After the lab reviews the order, we will inform you if any other lens related fee's, such as Oversize Fee, Custom Lens Surfacing Fee, Prism Fee, etc. will be needed to fill your lens request. You will be notified to confirm the additional fee prior to us proceeding with your order. If you choose not to confirm the additional fee, your lens order can be cancelled with-out being charged cancellation fee's. Not all lens requests are guaranteed. If we feel that we are unable to provide accurate,properly functioning and fitting lens requests, then we have the right to reject a lens order. 

14.) The Seg. Height (vertical measurement) of the lens is calculated by a formula which is for bi-focal, tri-focal and progressive lens requests. If a Seg. Height measurement is available that you would like for us to use, then you can provide this information in the 'Comments Section' of your order during check-out, and we will process this for you accordingly. However, please ensure that if you are providing a Seg. Height measurement, then it must be the same measurement used for the same exact eyeglass frames (same size as well) that you're purchasing from us, since the Seg. Height measurement is dependant on the frame size. If a Seg. height measurement is not provided by the customer or their eye care provider(s), then we will use our in-house formula for making the progressive lenses in your order. Our in-house formula is accurate in most cases, but is not guaranteed. We do suggest that this information is provided to ensure the accuracy of your bi-focal/tri-focal/progressive lens, however if this information is not provided, then we do not accept any responsibility of you having to adapt to the lens with this measurement. The Seg Height is not a required part of an eyeglass prescription, this information is to be provided by the customer [or their eye care provider(s)] as an additional request in their lens order. 

15.) Eyeglass frames purchased with-out additional lenses may come with the lenses that are sold this way from the vendor. This means that there may be a brand logo or any other engraving and/or marking(s) on the lenses which the manufacturer includes on them. Most eyeglass frames are intended to be used for prescription reasons, which means the lenses are usually meant to be replaced. We do offer plano lenses which can be made for these types of frames. These options can be seen on the lenses pricing page, under 'Non-Prescription/Plano' lenses. 

15.) Prices may change on contact lenses depending on the prescription paremeters provided. If there is any price difference on a contact lens order, the customer will be notified to confirm these fee's prior to processing. If the customer decides to cancel at this point (prior ro confirming the price difference), they can cancel the merchandise with no cancellation fee's.   
  
| Customer Privacy:  
---  
**1\. INTRODUCTION.** EYE TRENDS USA, INC., the owner of [GO-OPTIC.COM](http://go-optic.com/) (“us,” “we,” or “Company”), is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website (“the Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. 

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

2.1. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED 

(a) TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you, but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. 

(b) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED. In order for you to purchase products that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address); (2) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); (3) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, date of birth, and income) and (4) Medical Information (such as your prescription information and your prescribing doctor’s name and contact information). If you communicate with us by e-mail, telephone, facsimile or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. 

2.2. USES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED 

(a) COMPANY USE OF INFORMATION. We use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Site, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. We use your Medical Information to provide you with the appropriate products and services and to contact your doctor if we have any questions. 

(b) SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We also share Contact Data, Financial Data and Medical Information with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as billing, fulfillment of your order, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site and the delivery of goods and services. Those business partners have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Company. In addition, we maintain a procedure for you to review and request changes to your Personal Information; this procedure is described in Section 3.1, below. 

(c) USER CHOICE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. 

**3\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Service. We provide you with the capability to transmit you Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser. 

3.1. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION. We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may visit your personal profile by logging into your [GO-OPTIC.COM](http://go-optic.com/) account or you can also call us during our normal business hours at 877-634-2020 and one of our representatives will be happy to help update and/or access your information. Through your personal profile you may: (a) review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected; (b) choose whether or not you wish us to send you information about our company, or promotional material from some of our partners; and/or (c) choose whether or not you wish for us to share your Personal Information with third parties. 

3.2. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION. You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

3.3. PUBLIC INFORMATION. The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**4\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY.**   
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
